question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
        ]
    }
]
